Urvesh Vinod Dhangar () Featured

Software Engineer seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Solution Architecture, Java, Angular JS, Angular 6, JavaScript, Jquery, Ajax, HTML5, CSS, Spring MVC, Hibernate



Current Designation: Software Engineer -Java Total Experience: 3 Year(s) 8 Month(s)

Current Company: NeoSoft Technologies Notice Period: 1 Month

Current Location: Mumbai Highest Degree: PG Diploma [Computers]

Pref. Location: Mumbai, Pune, Hyderabad

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Software Engineer, Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Solution Architecture, Java, Angular JS, Angular

6, JavaScript, Jquery, Ajax, HTML5, CSS, Spring MVC, Hibernate

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

Summary

3.5 Years of experience in Web Application Development.

Currently working with Neosoft Technologies, as Software Engineer.

Last organization, Hug Innovations Corp., as Jr. Java Developer, CITI Solutions, as JAVA executive.

Proficiency in CORE JAVA, REST APIs.

Good understanding of Angular JS 1, Angular 6, Javascript, Jquery, Ajax, HTML, CSS, AWS, Eureka, Docker.

Hands on experience on Spring MVC frameworks.

Hands on experience SQL Database, Postgres and Mongo DB.

Handled Deployment responsibilities on AWS cloud.

Adopting pragmatic approach in improvising on solutions and resolving complex issues.

Proficiency at grasping new technical concepts quickly and utilizing the same in productive manner.

A team player with excellent analytical and communication skills.

Work Experience

NeoSoft Technologies as Software Engineer -Java Aug 2019 to Till Date

Citi Solutions as JAVA Executive Jun 2018 to Aug 2019

HUG INNOVATIONS as Jr. Java Developer

Apr 2017 to Jun 2018

Hug Innovations forays into developing gestures control technology with smart devices(Hug Smart Watch), Mobile apps(Hug Smart and Fit Android App) and PC software and Web apps for keeping history and maintenance of Hug smart watch users and HugFit users.

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from Mumbai University in 2016

PG: PG Diploma (Computers) from CDAD, Hyd in 2017

IT Skills

| Skill Name | Version Last Used | Experience |
|-----------------------|-------------------|------------|
| JAVA | | |
| Angular js 1 | | |
| Angular 6, Javascript | | |
| Jquery, Ajax | | |
| HTML5, CSS | | |
| Spring MVC, Hibernate | | |
| postman | | |
| Mongo,Postgres | | |
| AWS | | |
| Eclipse, NetBeans | | |
| Git, Tortoise SVN | | |
| Bitbucket, Docker | | |

Languages Known

| Language | Proficiency | Read | Write | Speak |
|----------|-------------|------|-------|-------|
| English | | | | |
| Hindi | | | | |
| Marathi | | | | |

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time